

SKILLS

UI/UX Design Web Design Prototyping User-Centered Design Visual Design Typography Branding / Marketing Conversion Rate Optimization Adobe XD Adobe Creative Cloud Windows | Mac OS HTML / CSS / Javascript

CURRENT POSITION

CONVERSION FANATICS | UX Designer & CRO Consultant

NOVEMBER 2018 - PRESENT | AUSTIN, TX

I am currently a UX designer on a lean team of CRO experts helping businesses across multiple industries increase engagement and revenue on their websites. I work with clients, project managers and developers to create A/B test plans, interactive prototypes and funnel analyses to increase conversions.

I have worked on over 40 websites spanning e-commerce, affiliate marketing, and software-as-a-service. I assist in monitoring A/B tests and collecting both quantitative and qualitative data in Google Analytics and CRO platforms like Convert Experiences and VWO.

RELEVANT PRIOR POSITIONS

FREELANCE DESIGNER

AUGUST 2017 - OCTOBER 2018 | AUSTIN, TX

SCOUT EXCHANGE | Lead Graphic Designer

AUGUST 2016 - AUGUST 2017 | BOSTON, MA

- · Promoted brand uniformity by creating and maintaining company print and digital style guide
- Supported sales initiatives and facilitated client retention by producing marketing collateral
- Supplied visual direction for offsite vendors and contractors across multiple departments
- Regularly presented ideas to VP of Marketing and C-Level stakeholders

HILL HOLLIDAY | Creative Intern

FEBRUARY 2016 - APRIL 2016 | BOSTON, MA

- · Concepted and executed designs in the creative department of a globally recognized advertising agency
- Designed logos, fliers, icons, and vector graphics
- Helped develop Facebook ads and print material for the healthcare team

BOSTON UNIVERSITY ADLAB

VP / Creative Director | AUG 2014 - MAY 2015

- Managed the art department for the country's largest student-run advertising agency
- Designed an e-commerce Squarespace website for a small startup with my creative team
- Taught students how to use creative software and basic design principles

EDUCATION

BACHELORS OF FINE ARTS - GRAPHIC DESIGN

Boston University, Magna Cum Laude 2015